[
	{
		"type": "NumberlineTutorialState",
		"desc_head": "NumberlineState_HEAD",
		"desc_body": "NumberlineState_BODY",
		"done": false,
		"saved": false,
		"trials": [
			[{
				"name": "NumberlineObject",
				"params": {
					"zero": 0,
					"ref": 1,
					"max": 32,
					"target": 9
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}],
			[{
				"name": "NumberlineObject",
				"params": {
					"zero": 0,
					"ref": 3,
					"max": 15,
					"target": 8
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}]

		]
	},
	{
		"type": "AdditionTutorialState",
		"desc_head": "ArithmeticState_HEAD",
		"desc_body": "ArithmeticState_BODY",
		"done": false,
		"saved": false,
		"trials": [
			[{
				"name": "ArithmeticHandler",
				"params": {
					"problem": "3+1=",
					"solution": 4
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}],
			[{
				"name": "ArithmeticHandler",
				"params": {
					"problem": "3+9=",
					"solution": 12
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}]

		]
	},
	{
		"type": "DifficultyFeedbackState",
		"desc_head": "ArithmeticState_HEAD",
		"desc_body": "ArithmeticState_BODY",
		"done": false,
		"saved": false,
		"trials": [
			[
				{
				"name": "FeedbackSliderObject",
				"params": {
					"zero": 0,
					"ref": 10,
					"max": 10,
					"target": 2
				}
			}
			]
		]
	},
	{
		"type": "MotivationFeedbackState",
		"desc_head": "ArithmeticState_HEAD",
		"desc_body": "ArithmeticState_BODY",
		"done": false,
		"saved": false,
		"trials": [
			[
				{
				"name": "FeedbackSliderObject",
				"params": {
					"zero": 0,
					"ref": 10,
					"max": 10,
					"target": 2
				}
			}
			]
		]
	},
	{
		"type": "NervousFeedbackState",
		"desc_head": "ArithmeticState_HEAD",
		"desc_body": "ArithmeticState_BODY",
		"done": false,
		"saved": false,
		"trials": [
			[
				{
				"name": "FeedbackSliderObject",
				"params": {
					"zero": 0,
					"ref": 10,
					"max": 10,
					"target": 2
				}
			}
			]
		]
	},
	{
		"type": "AdditionTutorialState",
		"desc_head": "ArithmeticState_HEAD",
		"desc_body": "ArithmeticState_BODY",
		"done": false,
		"saved": false,
		"trials": [
			[{
				"name": "ArithmeticHandler",
				"params": {
					"problem": "3+1=",
					"solution": 4
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}],
			[{
				"name": "ArithmeticHandler",
				"params": {
					"problem": "3+9=",
					"solution": 12
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}]

		]
	},
	{
		"type": "ArithmeticState",
		"desc_head": "ArithmeticState_HEAD",
		"desc_body": "ArithmeticState_BODY",
		"done": false,
		"saved": false,
		"trials": [
			[{
				"name": "ArithmeticHandler",
				"params": {
					"problem": "3+1=",
					"solution": 4
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}],
			[{
				"name": "ArithmeticHandler",
				"params": {
					"problem": "3+2=",
					"solution": 5
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}],
			[{
				"name": "ArithmeticHandler",
				"params": {
					"problem": "3+3=",
					"solution": 6
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}],
			[{
				"name": "ArithmeticHandler",
				"params": {
					"problem": "3+4=",
					"solution": 7
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}]
		]
	},	
	{
		"type": "NumberlineTutorialState",
		"desc_head": "NumberlineState_HEAD",
		"desc_body": "NumberlineState_BODY",
		"done": false,
		"saved": false,
		"trials": [
			[{
				"name": "NumberlineObject",
				"params": {
					"zero": 0,
					"ref": 2,
					"max": 19,
					"target": 9
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}],
			[{
				"name": "NumberlineObject",
				"params": {
					"zero": 0,
					"ref": 3,
					"max": 15,
					"target": 8
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}]

		]
	},
	{
		"type": "NumberlineState",
		"desc_head": "NumberlineState_HEAD",
		"desc_body": "NumberlineState_BODY",
		"done": false,
		"saved": false,
		"trials": [
			[{
				"name": "NumberlineObject",
				"params": {
					"zero": 0,
					"ref": 5,
					"max": 10,
					"target": 2
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}],
			[{
				"name": "NumberlineObject",
				"params": {
					"zero": 0,
					"ref": 3,
					"max": 25,
					"target": 8
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}]

		]
	},
	{
		"type": "SAVE",
		"done": false,
		"saved": false
	},
	{
		"type": "REDIRECT",
		"done": false,
		"saved": false,
		"to": {
			"type": "UnlockState"
		}
	},
	{
		"type": "AdditionTutorialState",
		"desc_head": "ArithmeticState_HEAD",
		"desc_body": "ArithmeticState_BODY",
		"done": false,
		"saved": false,
		"trials": [
			[{
				"name": "ArithmeticHandler",
				"params": {
					"problem": "3+1=",
					"solution": 4
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}],
			[{
				"name": "ArithmeticHandler",
				"params": {
					"problem": "3+9=",
					"solution": 12
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}]

		]
	},
	{
		"type": "ArithmeticState",
		"desc_head": "ArithmeticState_HEAD",
		"desc_body": "ArithmeticState_BODY",
		"done": false,
		"saved": false,
		"trials": [
			[{
				"name": "ArithmeticHandler",
				"params": {
					"problem": "3+1=",
					"solution": 4
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}],
			[{
				"name": "ArithmeticHandler",
				"params": {
					"problem": "3+2=",
					"solution": 5
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}],
			[{
				"name": "ArithmeticHandler",
				"params": {
					"problem": "3+3=",
					"solution": 6
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}],
			[{
				"name": "ArithmeticHandler",
				"params": {
					"problem": "3+4=",
					"solution": 7
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}]
		]
	},
	{
		"type": "SAVE",
		"done": false,
		"saved": false
	},
	{
		"type": "REDIRECT",
		"done": false,
		"saved": false,
		"to": {
			"type": "UnlockState"
		}
	},
	{
		"type": "SubtractionTutorialState",
		"desc_head": "ArithmeticState_HEAD",
		"desc_body": "ArithmeticState_BODY",
		"done": false,
		"saved": false,
		"trials": [
			[{
				"name": "ArithmeticHandler",
				"params": {
					"problem": "3-1=",
					"solution": 2
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}],
			[{
				"name": "ArithmeticHandler",
				"params": {
					"problem": "9-7=",
					"solution": 2
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}]

		]
	},
	{
		"type": "ArithmeticState",
		"desc_head": "ArithmeticState_HEAD",
		"desc_body": "ArithmeticState_BODY",
		"done": false,
		"saved": false,
		"trials": [
			[{
				"name": "ArithmeticHandler",
				"params": {
					"problem": "9-9=",
					"solution": 0
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}],
			[{
				"name": "ArithmeticHandler",
				"params": {
					"problem": "5-1=",
					"solution": 4
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}],
			[{
				"name": "ArithmeticHandler",
				"params": {
					"problem": "6-5=",
					"solution": 1
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}],
			[{
				"name": "ArithmeticHandler",
				"params": {
					"problem": "7-3=",
					"solution": 4
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}]
		]
	},
	{
		"type": "SAVE",
		"done": false,
		"saved": false
	},
	{
		"type": "REDIRECT",
		"done": false,
		"saved": false,
		"to": {
			"type": "UnlockState"
		}
	},
	{
		"type": "MultiplicationTutorialState",
		"desc_head": "ArithmeticState_HEAD",
		"desc_body": "ArithmeticState_BODY",
		"done": false,
		"saved": false,
		"trials": [
			[{
				"name": "ArithmeticHandler",
				"params": {
					"problem": "3x1=",
					"solution": 3
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}],
			[{
				"name": "ArithmeticHandler",
				"params": {
					"problem": "3x3=",
					"solution": 9
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}]

		]
	},
	{
		"type": "ArithmeticState",
		"desc_head": "ArithmeticState_HEAD",
		"desc_body": "ArithmeticState_BODY",
		"done": false,
		"saved": false,
		"trials": [
			[{
				"name": "ArithmeticHandler",
				"params": {
					"problem": "4x2=",
					"solution": 8
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}],
			[{
				"name": "ArithmeticHandler",
				"params": {
					"problem": "2x5=",
					"solution": 10
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}],
			[{
				"name": "ArithmeticHandler",
				"params": {
					"problem": "2x2=",
					"solution": 4
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}],
			[{
				"name": "ArithmeticHandler",
				"params": {
					"problem": "5x1=",
					"solution": 5
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}]
		]
	},
	{
		"type": "SAVE",
		"done": false,
		"saved": false
	},
	{
		"type": "REDIRECT",
		"done": false,
		"saved": false,
		"to": {
			"type": "UnlockState"
		}
	},
	{
		"type": "SymbolicNumberComparisonState",
		"desc_head": "SymbolicNumberComparison_HEAD",
		"desc_body": "SymbolicNumberComparison_BODY",
		"done": false,
		"saved": false,
		"trials": [
[{
				"name": "TaskHandler",
				"params": {
					"num_left": "3",
					"num_right": "1",
					"solution": 3
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}],
			[{
				"name": "TaskHandler",
				"params": {
					"num_left": "5",
					"num_right": "2",
					"solution": 5
				}
			}, {
				"name": "TotalTime"
			}]

		]
	},
	{
		"type": "SAVE",
		"done": false,
		"saved": false
	},
	{
		"type": "REDIRECT",
		"done": false,
		"saved": false,
		"to": {
			"type": "UnlockState"
		}
	}
]